<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News | Computer System Architecture Lab</title>
    <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>News</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://ku-csarch.github.io/media/icon_hufc4ea502f7977d2b250399d95297f953_357528_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to IEEE Transactions on Computers (Journal, SCIE)</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-tc22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-tc22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One paper was accepted to &lt;em&gt;IEEE Transactions on Computers&lt;/em&gt;. Our paper proposes &lt;em&gt;FLIXR&lt;/em&gt;, an efficient in-storage indexing mechanism in SSDs. &lt;em&gt;FLIXR&lt;/em&gt; builds and maintains the page-level indexes exploiting the SSD&amp;rsquo;s native page translation structures. &lt;em&gt;FLIXR&lt;/em&gt; automatically creates and updates new per-page indexes while new data is written to flash memory pages. FLIXR&amp;rsquo;s in-storage indexes are efficiently maintained in SSD&amp;rsquo;s flash translation layer alongside with page translation structures. Hence FLIXR can effectively reduce host processor&amp;rsquo;s heavy burdens for creating and maintaining index structures of large database structures.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jongmin presented at ICOIN 2022</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-icoin22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-icoin22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jongmin presented his research work regarding the new cache side-channel attack mechanism that exploits the vulnerabilities in the undo-based archtiectural defense solutions at the 36th International Conference on Information Networking (&lt;a href=&#34;http://icoin.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ICOIN 2022&lt;/a&gt;) held in Jeju-si, Jeju-do, South Kroea. Good job, Jongmin!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inje, Jonghyun, and Seungho presented at KSC 2021</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-ksc21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-ksc21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Inje, Jonghyun, and Seungho presented their research work at Korea Software Congress 2021 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://ksc2021.kiise.or.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;KSC 2021&lt;/a&gt;) held in Pyeongchang-gun, Gangwon-do. Inje presented his research on GCN inference performance with respect to graph features. Jonghyun presented his research on data cache of modern GPU architecture. Seungho presented his research on characteristics of GPU memory side-channels. Our lab members also attended the conference to have a great time. Good job, guys!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prof. Gunjae Koo will be serving on the program committee for GPGPU 2022</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/committee-gpgpu22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/committee-gpgpu22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Prof. Gunjae Koo will be serving on the program committee for the 14th Workshop on the General Purpose Processing Using GPU (&lt;a href=&#34;https://sarchlab.github.io/gpgpu2022/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;GPGPU 2022&lt;/a&gt;). GPGPU 2022 will be held in conjunction with &lt;a href=&#34;https://hpca-conf.org/2022/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;HPCA 2022&lt;/a&gt; in Seoul, South Korea. Please submit your best work!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to ICOIN 2022</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-icoin22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-icoin22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One paper was accepted to &lt;em&gt;Workshop on Information System Security (WISS)&lt;/em&gt; which will be held in conjunction with &lt;em&gt;International Conference on Information Networking (ICOIN) 2022&lt;/em&gt;. Our work reveals the undo-based protection schemes are still vulnerable to the modified Prime+Probe type attack that makes the restore buffer overflowed. Using the proposed restore buffer overflow attack approach, we reveal the attack can leak part of secret data successfully even though the processor is protected by the undo-based defense scheme.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Received the Korea University Insung Research Grant</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-insung21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-insung21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Computer System Architecture (CSArch) Lab received the Korea University Insung Research Grant to support the research on near data processing for genome analytics. We want to express our sincere gratitude to generous supporters who have contributed to Korea University.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two papers accepted to DATE 2022</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-date22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-date22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two papers were accepted to &lt;em&gt;Design, Automation and Test in Europe Conference (DATE) 2022&lt;/em&gt;. One paper proposes &lt;em&gt;CacheRewinder&lt;/em&gt;, an efficient architectural defense mechanism against transient execution attacks. &lt;em&gt;CacheRewinder&lt;/em&gt; exploits the underutilized write-back buffer entries to revoke cache updates done by speculative executions. Another paper presents &lt;em&gt;Stealth ECC&lt;/em&gt;, a cost-effective and strong memory protection scheme. &lt;em&gt;Stealth ECC&lt;/em&gt; exploits not-meaningful data fields to provide stronger error correction capability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to MDPI Electronics (Journal, SCIE)</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-mdpi21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-mdpi21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One paper was accepted to &lt;em&gt;MDPI Electronics&lt;/em&gt;. Our paper proposes &lt;em&gt;RT-Sniper&lt;/em&gt;, a software-based lightweight defense solution against cache side-channel attacks. &lt;em&gt;RT-Sniper&lt;/em&gt; pinpoints attack processes efficiently using a two-phased monitoring mechanism: core-level and process-level profiling. Hence, &lt;em&gt;RT-Sniper&lt;/em&gt; can effectively detect malicious processes with negligible performance overhead.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awarded the innovative research lab initiation grant (최초혁신실험실) from NRF</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/award-nrf21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/award-nrf21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Computer System Architecture (CSArch) Lab was awarded the innovative research lab initiation grant (최초혁신실험실) from National Research Foundation (NRF). The grant will allow us to set up fundamental research equipments for research on processor and memory system architecture. The amount of the grant is approximately $100,000. Thanks NRF!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inje presented at KCC 2021</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-kcc21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-kcc21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Inje presented his research on the characteristics of GCN inference models at Korea Computer Congress 2021 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://kcc2021.kiise.or.kr&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;KCC 2021&lt;/a&gt;) held in Seoguipo-si, Jeju-do. Our lab members also attended the conference to have a great time. Good job, Inje!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Received the outstanding young scientist grant (우수신진연구) from NRF</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-nrf21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-nrf21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Computer System Architecture (CSArch) Lab received funding from National Research Foundation (NRF) to support the research on the processor and memory architecture for neural networks using large graph structures. Prof. Gunjae Koo was awarded the outstanding young scientist grant (우수신진연구) which is a part of Basic Research Projects funded by Korean government. Thanks NRF!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
