<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conference | Computer System Architecture Lab</title>
    <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/category/conference/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://ku-csarch.github.io/category/conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Conference</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://ku-csarch.github.io/media/icon_hufc4ea502f7977d2b250399d95297f953_357528_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/category/conference/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to ICCD 2025</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accept-iccd25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accept-iccd25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One papers was accepted to the &lt;em&gt;International Conference on Computer Design (ICCD) 2025&lt;/em&gt;. Our paper proposes &lt;em&gt;FINEA&lt;/em&gt;, an efficient neural network architecture exploiting factorized input features. &lt;em&gt;FINEA&lt;/em&gt; leverages factorized dot-product operations by exploiting weight redundancy in quantized neural network models. &lt;em&gt;FINEA&lt;/em&gt; employs a processing engine that can excutes both factorized and unfactorized dot-product operations. In order to implement efficient factorized and unfactorized dot-product computations, &lt;em&gt;FINEA&lt;/em&gt; utilizes filter indexes derived from preprocessed weight tables.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taewoon presented at ICS 2025</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-ics25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-ics25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Taewoon presented his research work regarding an HBM-based PIM architecture and software optimizations for SpMV kernels at the International Conference on Supercomputing 2025 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://hpcrl.github.io/ICS2025-webpage/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ICS 2025&lt;/a&gt;). ICS is one of premier conferences on high-performance computing systems. Good job, Taewoon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to LCTES 2025</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-lctes25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-lctes25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One papers was accepted to the &lt;em&gt;the ACM SIGPLAN/SIGBED International Conference on Languages, Compilers, and Tools for Embedded Systems (LCTES) 2025&lt;/em&gt;. Our paper proposes &lt;em&gt;SSFFT&lt;/em&gt;, an efficient and optimized fast Fourier transform (FFT) kernel design approach for embedded GPUs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to ICS 2025</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-ics25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-ics25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One papers was accepted to the &lt;em&gt;ACM International Conference on Supercomputing (ICS) 2025&lt;/em&gt;. Our paper proposes &lt;em&gt;SparsePIM&lt;/em&gt;, an efficient HBM-based PIM architecture for SpMV kernels. &lt;em&gt;SparsePIM&lt;/em&gt; includes an efficient hardware architecture for SpMV computations and a sparse data allocation scheme in DRAM row. &lt;em&gt;SparsePIM&lt;/em&gt; also employ software-base optimizations to balance computation burdens acress multiple bank groups. By combiging hardware and software approaches, &lt;em&gt;SparsePIM&lt;/em&gt; can improve SpMV computations dramatically on HBM-based PIM architecture.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jihun presented at DATE 2025</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-date25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-date25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jihun presented his research work regarding a hybrid GNN accelerator architecture at the Design, Automation and Test in Europe Conference 2025 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.date-conference.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;DATE 2025&lt;/a&gt;). DATE is one of top-tier conferences on design automation, hardware design and architecture. Good job, Jihun!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to ISPASS 2025</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-ispass25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-ispass25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One papers was accepted to the &lt;em&gt;2025 IEEE International Symposium on Performance Analysis of Systems and Software (ISPASS)&lt;/em&gt;. Our paper proposes hierarchical traversal stack design approach using shared memory for GPU ray tracing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to DATE 2025</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-date25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-date25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One papers was accepted to the &lt;em&gt;Design, Automation and Test in Europe Conference (DATE) 2025&lt;/em&gt;. Our paper proposes &lt;em&gt;HyMM&lt;/em&gt;, an efficient sparse-dense matrix multiplication accelerator architecture for GCNs. &lt;em&gt;HyMM&lt;/em&gt; implements a hybrid sparse-dense matrix multiplication dataflow to exploit the data locality observed in graph structures in GCNs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaewon presented at NVMSA 2024</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-nvmsa24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-nvmsa24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jaewon presented his research work regarding an efficient garbage collection scheme for remap-based SSDs at the 13th IEEE Non-Volatile Memory Systems and Applications (&lt;a href=&#34;https://nvmsa2024.github.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;NVMSA 2024&lt;/a&gt;). Good job, Jaewon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to ICPP 2024</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-icpp24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-icpp24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One paper was accepted to the &lt;em&gt;53nd International Conference on Parallel Processing (ICPP 2024)&lt;/em&gt;. Our research paper proposes &lt;em&gt;VitBit&lt;/em&gt;, an efficient register operand packing scheme for embedded GPUs. &lt;em&gt;VitBit&lt;/em&gt; packs low-precision integer data for parallel computation of integer and floating-point engines. Hence, &lt;em&gt;VitBit&lt;/em&gt; can effectively increase the arithmetic density of GPU computations to improve the throughput of embedded GPUs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to NVMSA 2024</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-nvmsa24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-nvmsa24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One paper was accepted to the &lt;em&gt;the 13th IEEE Non-Volatile Memory Systems and Applications Symposium (NVMSA)&lt;/em&gt;. Our research work proposes an effieicnt garbage collection mechanism, called &lt;em&gt;ColdMap&lt;/em&gt;, which can extend the lifetime of SSD by exploiting multi-page mapping information.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prof. Gunjae Koo presented at ICCE-Asia 2023</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-iccea23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-iccea23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Prof. Gunjae Koo was invited to present for one of the special sessions at the IEEE/IEIE International Conference on Consumer Electronics Asia 2023 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://icce-asia2023.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ICCE-Asis 2023&lt;/a&gt;). He made a talk regarding his research on GPU memory subsystem.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonghyun presented at ICPP 2023</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-icpp23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-icpp23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jonghyun presented his research work regarding an efficient memory controller scheme for GPUs at the International Conference on Parallel Processing 2023 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://icpp23.sci.utah.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ICPP 2023&lt;/a&gt;). ICPP is one of premier conferences on parallel computing and architecture. Good job, Jonghyun!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted to ICPP 2023</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-icpp23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-icpp23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One paper was accepted to the &lt;em&gt;52nd International Conference on Parallel Processing (ICPP 2023)&lt;/em&gt;. Our research paper proposes &lt;em&gt;Warped-MC&lt;/em&gt;, an efficient memory controller scheme for modern GPUs. &lt;em&gt;Warped-MC&lt;/em&gt; mitigates the latency divergence observed in a warp that create multiple outstanding memory requests. Hence, &lt;em&gt;Warped-MC&lt;/em&gt; can effectively reduce a long-tail of load warp execution time to improve the overall GPU performance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jongmin presented at DATE 2022</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-date22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-date22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jongmin presented his research work regarding an efficient architectural defense mechanism against transient execution attacks at the Design, Automation and Test in Europe Conference 2022 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.date-conference.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;DATE 2022&lt;/a&gt;). DATE is one of top-tier conferences on EDA and VLSI design. Good job, Jongmin!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jongmin presented at ICOIN 2022</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-icoin22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/present-icoin22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jongmin presented his research work regarding the new cache side-channel attack mechanism that exploits the vulnerabilities in the undo-based archtiectural defense solutions at the 36th International Conference on Information Networking (&lt;a href=&#34;http://icoin.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ICOIN 2022&lt;/a&gt;) held in Jeju-si, Jeju-do, South Kroea. Good job, Jongmin!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two papers accepted to DATE 2022</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-date22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/accepted-date22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two papers were accepted to the &lt;em&gt;Design, Automation and Test in Europe Conference (DATE) 2022&lt;/em&gt;. One paper proposes &lt;em&gt;CacheRewinder&lt;/em&gt;, an efficient architectural defense mechanism against transient execution attacks. &lt;em&gt;CacheRewinder&lt;/em&gt; exploits the underutilized write-back buffer entries to revoke cache updates done by speculative executions. Another paper presents &lt;em&gt;Stealth ECC&lt;/em&gt;, a cost-effective and strong memory protection scheme. &lt;em&gt;Stealth ECC&lt;/em&gt; exploits not-meaningful data fields to provide stronger error correction capability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
