<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Funding | Computer System Architecture Lab</title>
    <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/category/funding/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://ku-csarch.github.io/category/funding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Funding</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://ku-csarch.github.io/media/icon_hufc4ea502f7977d2b250399d95297f953_357528_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Funding</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/category/funding/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected as a recipient for the project support from IITP</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-iitp25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-iitp25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Computer System Architecture (CSArch) Lab received funding from Institute for Information &amp;amp; Communication Technology Planning &amp;amp; Evaluation (IITP) to support the research on development of chiplet-based hub SoC for on-device AI. Prof. Gunjae Koo will be working as a Co-PI of the research project. Thanks IITP!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Received the Korea University Insung Research Grant</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-insung21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-insung21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Computer System Architecture (CSArch) Lab received the Korea University Insung Research Grant to support the research on near data processing for genome analytics. We want to express our sincere gratitude to generous supporters who have contributed to Korea University.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awarded the innovative research lab initiation grant (최초혁신실험실) from NRF</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/award-nrf21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/award-nrf21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Computer System Architecture (CSArch) Lab was awarded the innovative research lab initiation grant (최초혁신실험실) from National Research Foundation (NRF). The grant will allow us to set up fundamental research equipments for research on processor and memory system architecture. The amount of the grant is approximately $100,000. Thanks NRF!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Received the outstanding young scientist grant (우수신진연구) from NRF</title>
      <link>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-nrf21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ku-csarch.github.io/post/grant-nrf21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Computer System Architecture (CSArch) Lab received funding from National Research Foundation (NRF) to support the research on the processor and memory architecture for neural networks using large graph structures. Prof. Gunjae Koo was awarded the outstanding young scientist grant (우수신진연구) which is a part of Basic Research Projects funded by Korean government. Thanks NRF!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
